Indian Neck Folk Festival collection, 1961-2015
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Indian Neck Folk Festival collection 1961-2015
AFC 2016/002
6986 items; 7 containers; 4.5 linear feet.
48 sound cassettes (DAT): digital.
284 sound cassettes: analog.
65 sound tape reels: analog; 7 in.
10 sound tape reels: analog; 10 in.
44 sound discs (CD-R): digital; 4 3/4 in.
3 videocassettes (VHS): sound, color; 1/2 in.
3 video discs (DVD): digital, sound, color; 4 3/4 in.
moving images: 152 video files (MOV and MP4): digital.
graphic images: 4453 photographs: digital, JPEG files, color.
graphic images: 54 photographs: film negatives, black-and-white; 35 mm
graphic images: 654 photographs: photographic prints; 8 x 11 in. and smaller.
sound recordings: 249 sound files: digital, WAV files.
manuscripts: 50 items (PDF, DOC): text files.
manuscripts: 1050 items.
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of audio recordings of folk festival concerts, workshops, and informal events, produced at various locations in Connecticut and Pennsylvania by the Indian Neck Folk Festival from about 1961-2015. The collection also includes papers, photographs, videocassettes, posters, and digital files.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Beers, Bob, 1920-1972; Beers, Evelyne; Berkeley, Roy, 1935-2009; Blaustein, Richard; Bok, Gordon; Broudy, Saul; Cohen, John, 1932-2019.; Davis, Gary, 1896-1972; Dylan, Bob, 1941-; Eberhart, Jon; Goss, Linda; Hartman-Berrier, Jay; Haslam, Cliff; Hickerson, Joseph C. (Joseph Charles), 1935-; Hickerson, Kathryn W.; Jackson, John, 1924-2002; MacArthur, Margaret, 1928-2006; McClatchy, Debby; McCoury, Del, 1939-; McCutcheon, John, 1952-; Moloney, Mick, 1944-2022; O'Donnell, Eugene, 1932-; Paley, Tom; Peirce, Maggi Kerr, 1931-; Rosenbaum, Art; Schneyer, Helen; Seeger, Mike, 1933-2009; Staines, Bill; Tuft, Harry M.; Van Ronk, Dave; Wallace, Andy
Organizations
Ian & Sylvia; Indian Neck Folk Festival, collector.; Indian Neck Folk Festival.; Pennsylvania Folk Festival (1981-1985: Chambersburg, Pa.)
Subjects
Folk festivals--Connecticut.; Folk festivals--Pennsylvania.; Folk festivals--United States.; Folk music festivals--Connecticut.; Folk music festivals--Pennsylvania.; Folk music--Connecticut.; Folk music--Pennsylvania.; Folk songs, English.; Popular music--1961-1970.; Popular music--1971-1980.; Popular music--1981-1990.; Popular music--1991-2000.; Popular music--2001-2010.
Places
Falls Village (Conn.); Falls Village (Conn.), event place.; Harrisburg (Pa.); Harrisburg (Pa.), event place.; New Haven (Conn.); New Haven (Conn.), event place.
Form/Genre
Manuscripts.; Photographs.; Sound recordings.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: I. Manuscripts; II. Sound Recordings; III. Graphic Materials; IV. Moving Images; V. Optical Media; VI. Oversize materials. Arrangement reflects the intellectual/chronological order rather than the physical numbering of items.
Acquisition
Indian Neck Folk Festival collection; 2016.
Related Material
A related collection is AFC 2016/055, Christopher Moore collection of Indian Neck Folk Festival and other recordings. http://lccn.loc.gov/2016655337. Collection of audio recordings of performances at the Indian Neck Folk Festival from about 1965-1972, as well as at concerts and informal folk music events in Connecticut, in Cambridge, Massachusetts, and the 1968 Old-Time Fiddlers Contest in Craftsbury Common, Vermont. Bulk of the recordings were made from 1964 to 1975, a few in 1982.
Access and Restrictions
Collection is open for research; access to collection materials may be restricted. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Additional Formats Available
Selected analog recordings have digital preservation masters.
Biographical Note
The Indian Neck Folk Festival was founded by student members of the Yale University Folk Music Club, including musician John Cohen, and others. The festival was held in 1958, 1960, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1966, and then was held annually on a weekend in May. The group raised money for the festival by hosting a series of public folk music concerts on the Yale University campus and other locations. In 1970 the non-profit organization cut its ties with Yale, and moved the festival to a camp facility on Indian Neck Point in Branford, Connecticut. Jay Hartman-Berrier was the Indian Neck Folk Festival director for 51 years until her death in March 2017. In the early 1980s Jay Hartman-Berrier started a folk music concert series at Harrisburg Area Community College under the Indian Neck name, which ran for 5 years and then was taken over by the Susquehanna Folk Music Society. Because of her expertise and reputation, in 1983 she was approached by a group of five small colleges in Central Pennsylvania to organize the Pennsylvania Folk Festival, which ran for three years, showcasing Pennsylvania folk traditions, musicians and groups. The Indian Neck Folk Festival continued to be held during this time, by invitation only, in Falls Village, Connecticut. Since Hartman-Berrier's passing, the festival continues on with a different name.
Scope and Content
Collection of audio recordings of folk festival concerts, workshops, and informal events, produced at various locations in Connecticut and Pennsylvania by the Indian Neck Folk Festival from about 1961-2015. The collection also includes papers, photographs, videocassettes, posters, and digital files. The Indian Neck Folk Festival was an invitation-only folk music gathering held annually in May at a camp facility in Connecticut. The collection documents the relationships, activities, and music that this community shared over the course of several generations. Includes documentation about planning and organizing the Indian Neck Folk Festivals, as well as photographs and sound recordings of public concerts and events at Yale University, Harrisburg Area Community College, and the Pennsylvania Folk Festival. The Indian Neck Folk Festival and concerts featured various performers, including Bob Dylan, Dave van Ronk, Rev. Gary Davis, John Hammond, Big Joe Williams, Ian and Sylvia, Gordon Bok, Sara Grey, Kenneth S. Goldstein, Debby McClatchy, Helen Schneyer, Del McCoury and the Dixie Pals, Mike Seeger, Tony Trischka and Skyline, the Paton family, Mick Moloney and Eugene O'Donnell, Ed Trickett, Ann Mayo Muir, Stan Rogers, Utah Phillips, Sparky Rucker, John McCutcheon, Grey Larsen, Michael Cooney, Bill Staines, Joe Hickerson and Kathy Hickerson, Alistair Anderson, Kinvara, John Jackson, Sally Rogers and Howie Bursen, Barbara Carns, Philippe Bruneau, Lucy Simpson, Margaret MacArthur, Lani Herrmann, Pricilla Herdman, Jon Wilcox, Linda Goss, Elizabeth LaPrelle, Ken Perlman, and many others.
Container List
- Series I: Manuscripts, 1966-2015
  - Subseries A: Indian Neck Folk Festival
    Documentation from the planning of the Indian Neck Folk Festival, including contracts, financial reports, scholarship fund information, board of directors information, room assignments for attendees, menus, festival invitations, newsletters, correspondence, and other information about the festival. From 1969-2015, the festival was held at Camp Isabella Freedman in Falls Village, Connecticut.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, April 29-May 5, 1966 (Box-folder 1/1)
      Location: Castle Hotel, Old Saybrook, CT. Includes letter of invitation to the festival from Jack Bertman. Includes pages from guest book with attendees names and contacts, as well as pages about lodging requirements for each attendee.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12-14, 1967 (Box-folder 1/2)
      Location: Klar Krest Resort, Moodus, CT.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, April 26-28, 1968 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2-4, 1969 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1-3, 1970 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 7-9, 1971 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12-15, 1972 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11-14, 1973 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10-13, 1974 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 9-12, 1975 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 7-10, 1976 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 6-8, 1977 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12-15, 1978 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11-14, 1979 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 9-12, 1980 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 8-11, 1981 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 7-10, 1982 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 6-9, 1983 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11-14, 1984 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10-13, 1985 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 9-12, 1986 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 8-11, 1987 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 6-9, 1988 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12-15, 1989 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11-14, 1990 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10-13, 1991 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 8-11, 1992 (Box-folder 1/27)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 7-10, 1993 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 6-9, 1994 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12-15, 1995 (Box-folder 1/30)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10-13, 1996 (Box-folder 1/31)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 9-12, 1998 (Box-folder 1/32)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 8-11, 1998 (Box-folder 1/33)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 7-10, 1999 (Box-folder 1/34)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12-15, 2000 (Box-folder 1/35)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11-14, 2001 (Box-folder 1/36)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10-13, 2002 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 9-12, 2003 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 7-10, 2004 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 6-9, 2005 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12-15, 2006 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11-14, 2007 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 9-12, 2008 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 8-11, 2009 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 7-10, 2010 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 6-9, 2011 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11-14, 2012 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10-13, 2013 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 9-12, 2014 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - INFF (Indian Neck Folk Festival) Folk Music Archives Conference, May 7-8, 2015 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Folk Music Archives Conference, May 7-8, 2015 (Box-folder 2/15)
      Presented by the Indian Neck Folk Festival. Includes conference schedule, biographies of presenters and participants, and list of resources.
  - Subseries B: Harrisburg Concert Series
    Documentation from concert series in Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, hosted by Indian Neck Folk Festival group and the Harrisburg Area Community College Cultural Events Series.
    - Materials from Harrisburg Concert Series, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2/16)
      Includes fliers, programs, press releases, and newspaper clippings about the Harrisburg Concert Series. Also includes grant from the Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, as well as contracts/agreements with performers.
    - Guest book, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2/17)
      Signed guest book from Harrisburg Concert Series.
    - Materials from Harrisburg Concert Series, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 3/1)
      Includes fliers, programs, press releases, and newspaper clippings about the Harrisburg Concert Series. Includes posters for Bill Staines, Gordon Bok, and Mike Seeger concerts. Also includes Pennsylvania Council on the Arts grant project description, schedule, and budget, as well as signed contracts/agreements with performers.
    - Materials from Harrisburg Concert Series, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 3/2)
      Includes fliers, programs, press releases, and newspaper clippings about the Harrisburg Concert Series. Also includes Pennsylvania Council on the Arts grant narrative and financial reports, as well as signed contracts/agreements with performers, such as Utah Phillips, Sparky Rucker, and Mick Moloney.
    - Materials from Harrisburg Concert Series, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 3/3)
      Includes fliers, programs, press releases, and newspaper clippings about the Harrisburg Concert Series. Also includes Pennsylvania Council on the Arts grant project description, schedule, and budget, as well as signed contracts/agreements with performers, such as Malcolm Dalglish, Larsen and Sutherland, Joe and Kathy Hickerson, and the Broken String Band.
    - Materials from Harrisburg Concert Series, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 3/4)
      Includes fliers and press releases about the Harrisburg Concert Series. Also includes Pennsylvania Council on the Arts grant project description, schedule, and budget, as well as signed contracts/agreements with performers, such as the Critton Hollow String Band and the Broken String Band.
  - Subseries C: Pennsylvania Folk Festival
    Traditional folk festival planned by the Central Pennsylvania Consortium and held at Wilson College in Chambersburg, Pennsylvania.
    - 1981 Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27-28, 1981 (Box-folder 3/5)
      Planning material and program/schedule for the first Pennsylvania Folk Festival in 1981. Includes photographs of the festival's performers, including Maggi Peirce and Bill Staines.
    - 1982 Pennsylvania Folk Festival, February 26-27, 1982 (Box-folder 3/6)
      Programs, press releases, and newspaper clippings about the Pennsylvania Folk Festival in 1982. Includes invitation letter to festival from Jay Hartman-Berrier, as well as Pennsylvania Council on the Arts grant project description, schedule, and financial report.
    - 1983 Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 25-27, 1983 (Box-folder 3/7)
      Programs, press releases, and newspaper clippings about the third Pennsylvania Folk Festival in 1983. Includes invitation letter to festival from Jay Hartman-Berrier, as well as Pennsylvania Council on the Arts grant project description, schedule, and financial report, and narrative report of grant-in aid.
    - 1984 Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23-25, 1984 (Box-folder 3/8)
      Programs, tickets, press releases, and newspaper clippings about fourth Pennsylvania Folk Festival in 1984. Includes invitation letter to festival from Jay Hartman-Berrier, as well as Pennsylvania Council on the Arts grant description and correspondence. Also includes performance contracts with festival performers.
    - 1985 Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 22-24, 1985 (Box-folder 3/9)
      Programs, tickets, press releases, and other materials about the Pennsylvania Folk Festival in 1985. Includes invitation letter to festival from Jay Hartman-Berrier, as well as Pennsylvania Council on the Arts grant description and correspondence.
    - Pennsylvania craftsmen, ca. 1980-1985 (Box-folder 3/10)
      Lists of names and contacts of craftsmen from Pennsylvania. Includes catalog from the National Handweavers' Show.
    - Promotional materials, ca. 1978-1981 (Box-folder 3/11)
      Articles and press materials for musicians, such as Maggi Peirce, Utah Phillips, the Boys of the Lough, and John McCutcheon.
    - Collection inventory materials, ca. 2013-2016 (Box-folder 3/12)
      Includes Gift Agreement for the Indian Neck Folk Festival collection, box-level inventory and inventory of physical media, and recorded media notes.
    - Sound recording documentation, ca. 1961-1976 (Box-folder 3/13)
      Includes container documentation for sound recordings from Indian Neck Folk Festival concerts and events. Information about song titles and performers is documented.
- Series II: Sound Recordings, 1961-2014
  See Appendix A for more detailed information about concerts, performers, song titles, and instrumentation. Many of the sound recordings have been digitized and are accessible in the Folklife Reading Room. There are 249 additional digital audio files (WAV) in Series V: Optical Media.
  - 1961 concert at Woolsey Hall, Mondowese House, Yale University, 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR001)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert featuring Sally Schoenfeld, George Lory, Bob Dylan, Gina Ross, Mark Spoelstra, and the Greenbriar Boys (Ralph Rinzler, guitar; Bob Yellin; Johnny Herald, and Gary Garnett of the Gray Sky Boys, bass).
  - 1961 concert at Woolsey Hall, Mondowese House, Yale University, June 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR002)
    1961 Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, the Mondowese House, Yale University, June, 1961. Includes the Greenbriar Boys, Mike Levy and Dave Smoley, Phyllis Henry, Luke and Ellen Faust, and Arnie Feldman.
  - 1961 concert at Woolsey Hall, Mondowese House, Yale University, 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR003)
    1961 Indian Neck Folk Festival concert with Reverend Gary Davis and Jim Kweskin.
  - 1961 concert at Woolsey Hall, Mondowese House, Yale University, 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR004)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert featuring Arnie Feldman, Zola, Bill Noss and Gordon Snow, Winnie Winston and Bill Keith, Buffy Sainte-Marie, and Sandy Bull.
  - 1961 concert at Woolsey Hall, Mondowese House, Yale University, 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR005)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert featuring Angus Godwin (with Evelyne Beers) and Mitch Greenhill and Tom Rush (with Connie Green and Gary Ardette).
  - 1961 concert at Woolsey Hall, Mondowese House, Yale University, June 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR006)
    Reel 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert featuring Zola Alcantara!, Jackie Washington, Molly Scott, and Connie Green.
  - 1961 concert at Woolsey Hall, Mondowese House, Yale University, 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR007)
    Reel 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert featuring Angus Godwin, Fiddler and Evelyne Beers, Mike Callahan and Don Miller, Lori Holland, and Annie Bird with Ralph Rinzler and Dave Levy.
  - 1961 concert at Woolsey Hall, Mondowese House, Yale University, 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR008)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert featuring Jackie Washington and Carolyn Gold, and Fiddler and Evelyne Beers.
  - 1961 concert at Woolsey Hall, Mondowese House, Yale University, 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR009)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert featuring Fiddler and Evelyne Beers, Annie Bird, Roy Campbell, Allan Block, and Shel Kagan.
  - 1961 concert at Woolsey Hall, Mondowese House, Yale University, 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR010)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert featuring Reverend Gary Davis, Fiddler and Evelyne Beers, Hedy West, and the Grey Sky Boys.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 1, 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR144)
    Reel 1 of 4. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Concert dub.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 1, 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR145)
    Reel 2 of 4. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Concert dub.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 1, 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR146)
    Reel 3 of 4. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Concert dub.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 1, 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR147)
    Reel 4 of 4. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Concert dub.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 22, 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR148)
    Reel 1 of 2. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Big Joe Williams concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 22, 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR149)
    Reel 2 of 2. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Big Joe Williams concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 22, 1965, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR318)
    Big Joe Williams concert. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Copies of 7-inch reels (SR148-SR149).
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, April 30, 1966, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR150)
    Reel 1 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Richard Blaustein and Tim Woodbridge, Thomas Heiman, The Diminished Seven, Richard Jaffee, Ohio River Boys, Dan Isaacson and family, Roy Berkeley with Tim Woodbridge and Peter Childs, Shirley Keller, and Karl Ecklund.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, April 30, 1966, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR151)
    Reel 2 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring The Pennywhistlers, David and Megan Marash with Charlie Cardini, Ed Freeman, The Mother Bay State Entertainers, Roger Sprung, Rick and Lorraine Lee, Ed Badeaux, Art Rosenbaum and Allan Block, and Anna Peretz with Charlie Cardini and Pete Childs.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, April 30, 1966, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR152)
    Reel 3 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Pete Childs, Brock Sherman and Pete Peterson, Ray Prinz, Geoff Noyes, Bob Jones and Jack Hubert, Jim Rooney and Clay Jackson, Arnold Feldman, Richard Blaustein, and Billy Hamilton, Jon Scoville, Bob Jones, Jack Parmley and company, and Mel Lyman.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, April 30, 1966, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR153)
    Reel 4 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Mel Lyman, Lew Sellinger, Richard Blaustein, Tim Woodbridge, Pete Peterson, John MacDonald, John Burke, Bob Bell, and others (likely Allan Block and Arnie Feldman).
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, April 30, 1966, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR154)
    Reel 5 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert. "More Friday night old-timey with Sellinger, Blaustein, Woodbridge, Peterson, MacDonald."
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, November 12, 1966, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR155)
    Reel 1 of 3. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Ian and Sylvia with David Rae, lead guitar. Performing at Woolsey Hall, Yale University. Performed and recorded November 12, 1966. Copied from 3 tapes 4/20/1993. For song list see Appendix A.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, November 12, 1966, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR156)
    Reel 2 of 3. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Ian and Sylvia with David Rae, lead guitar. Performing at Woolsey Hall, Yale University. Performed and recorded November 12, 1966. For song list see Appendix A.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, November 12, 1966, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR157)
    Reel 3 of 3. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Ian and Sylvia with David Rae, lead guitar. Performing at Woolsey Hall, Yale University. Performed and recorded November 12, 1966. For song list see Appendix A.